https://www.cgi.com/en/global-privacy

Website Privacy Policy
At CGI, we are transparent about how we use your personal data when visiting our website (the “Website”). The purpose of this website privacy policy (the “Policy”) is to inform you about our practices in connection with the collection, use and disclosure of the personal data you make available to us. Furthermore, this Policy describes the type of data that may be collected by our use of cookies and other technologies across our Website.
This Policy applies to www.cgi.com and any authorized sub-sites that expressly adopt, display or link back to this Policy.
For California residents, see the CGI Notice for California Consumers.
Collection and use of personal information
We may collect personal data that you voluntarily provide to us when:
You request information about our services;
You submit questions to us;
You subscribe to our services; and
You choose to submit your resume in relation to career opportunities posted on our Website.
The personal data provided by you may be used to communicate with you in connection with your various inquiries and subscriptions or to consider you for employment purposes, and will be kept for the time period in which it is necessary for the purpose it was collected.
Disclosure of personal data
Your personal data may be shared outside of the country where you are located, with relevant CGI affiliates in charge of dealing with your inquiries, subscriptions or applications. The list of CGI affiliates and country of location is available from https://www.cgi.com/offices.
Where such transfers take place, CGI has implemented internal privacy policies and processes that ensure a high level of protection of your personal information across CGI affiliates, irrespective of where the personal information originates or is processed.
We may also share data provided by you with service providers that we retain to perform services on our behalf, such as third party content providers that facilitate event registrations, support displaying CGI videos, and enable sharing of CGI content in social media. These providers are contractually limited from using or disclosing the data except as is necessary to provide services to us or to comply with legal requirements. In addition, we may share personal information at your discretion, such as when you enroll in a webinar or pay for a service. Furthermore, we may disclose data about you where we are required or permitted by law to do so.
Our security measures to protect personal data
We maintain reasonable physical, technical and administrative safeguards to help protect against the unauthorized access, use and disclosure of personal data you voluntarily provide to us.
It should be noted that we cannot be held responsible for any personal data you share or post on public spaces, such as our blogs. Such public spaces may be consulted or viewed by anyone visiting our Website and, as such, falls outside the scope of this Policy.
Access, review and correction
You have the right to access your personal data. For legitimate purposes, you can rectify or oppose to the processing of your personal data. You also are entitled to ask to receive your personal data in a structured and standard format. In case of any such request or complaint, please send an email to privacy@cgi.com or write to CGI's Chief Data Protection Office (Legal Department) CGI Inc., 1350 René-Lévesque Blvd. West, Montréal, Canada, QC H3G 1T4.
To the extent permitted by applicable law, where CGI would not address properly your request, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the competent data protection authority.
Use of technology: cookies and logs
Cookies
We may collect data in connection with your visit to our Website through the use of cookies. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. We may also collect data that your browser sends us, such as your IP address, browser type, location, language, access time and referring Web site addresses.
Such data may be used to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track your movements around the site and to gather demographic data about our visitor base as a whole. The data gathered by these cookies is in the form of aggregated anonymous data.
We use different types of cookies as summarized below:
Strictly necessary cookies
These cookies are strictly necessary to offer you the basic functionalities of our Website, to deliver the services you have specifically asked for, and to remember your settings, such as detection of your language preferences in English or French.
Name
Retention period
Language
12 months
SESSIONID
24 days
Performance cookies
This cookie is set by Akamai to accelerate the page load time of pages to improve performance.
Name
Retention period
AKA_A2
1 hour
Functionality cookies
These cookies remember choices you make to improve your experience when returning to pages requiring an acceptance of login.
Name
Page/Component
Retention period
eea
EEA share purchase plan prospectus disclaimer acceptance page
Expires following the user’s session
cookieValue
Earnings Webcast disclaimer
12 months
cookieconsent_dismissed
Cookie consent bar acceptance
12 months
Drupal.visitor.is_logged_in
Analytic cookies
These cookies collect data to help us understand how our visitors use the Website and how we can improve the Website.
Name
Retention period
Google Analytics (_gat)
10 minutes
Google Analytics (_ga)
14 months
Google Analytics (_gid)
24 hours
You may choose to disable all or certain cookies on your computer by modifying your web browser. Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit the tutorials provided by your web browser provider such as:
Cookie management in Internet Explorer
Cookie management in Google Chrome
Cookie management in Apple Safari
Cookie management in Opera
Please note that if you choose to disable cookies, this may impact the performance of the Website during your visit.
Logs
CGI may also use logs to collect data about visitors’ use of the Website. CGI may review server logs for security purposes, for example, to detect intrusions into our network. Server log data, which contains visitors' IP addresses, could in instances of criminal malfeasance be used to trace and identify individuals. In such instances, raw data logs would be shared with appropriate investigative bodies authorized to investigate such breaches of security. Like cookies, logs do not cross reference the data automatically collected with any type of personal data that is voluntarily offered by you on or through this Website.
Links to non-CGI websites and third-party applications
This Website may contain links to third-party websites and third-party applications that are not affiliated with CGI (such as YouTube and Vimeo for videos, Google for Maps, ShareThis for social sharing, Twitter and Facebook feeds, Digicast for webcasts, and more). CGI does not in any way endorse or make any representations about such third-party websites and applications. As such, CGI is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such third-party websites and applications that are subject to their own privacy policies. If you choose to access such links, we encourage you to review all third-party site privacy policies before submitting any of your data.
Changes
CGI reserves the right to make changes to this Policy from time to time without notice.
Privacy questions
For additional information about our online privacy practices, please contact us at privacy@cgi.com.
